Are you watching me?
Do I look dashing?
Nobody says "dashing."
James Bond says "dashing."
You think you're James Bond?
I could be James Bond.
I've got Connery's swagger.
Definitely
Daniel Craig's physique.
Lazenby's...
I have no idea
what he's known for.
You okay?
I had an interesting conversation
with Louis last night.
He said I should be careful
of you and Rachel.
Do I have anything
to worry about?
He hates me. And he's just trying
to get to me through you.
So you never...
You've got nothing
to worry about.
She's just a friend.
- Okay.
- And I am late.
- I'll call.
- Okay.
We should go out.
I thought this is going out.
No, I mean, um...
You and me and Rachel
should go on a double date.
Does she have a boyfriend?
(Stuttering) I don't know.
No. I mean...
Going on a double date with somebody
from work might be kind of...
Weird.
If I get to know her,
then I won't worry.
It will be fun.
Just a couple of friends
going out, right?
Awesome.
(Sighs)
A cab? Someone steal your bike?
I have a lot on my mind.
It's a safety issue.
- What are you talking about?
- Louis.
He told Jenny about
Rachel and me.
It was one kiss,
and she kissed me. I...
Okay, soap opera, just
give me my documents.
Harvey.
Cameron.
How the hell are you?
- It's good to see you.
- Wow.
Too damn long.
Cameron Dennis,
district attorney.
Meet Mike Ross, my associate.
I guess that makes you
his Harvey.
- Sorry?
- Harvey was my associate.
I taught him
everything he knows.
Best Ada to come up since...
- Me.
- You taught him.
"Never go to court."
That's me.
"It's not about caring,
"it's about winning." Me.
- No way. Harvey's Harvey.
- Yeah. Exactly.
We should, uh,
catch up. Have lunch.
Hey, you know what? This is crazy.
I'm free for dinner tonight.
Just cancel whatever you have and tell
Jessica I demanded
that you clear your schedule.
Dinner it is. It will be nice.
That's my boy.
All right. You know where
to find me. 8:00.
Glad I ran into you, Harvey.
Kyle: It's pretty
good work. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Ross, you still work here?
- Funny.
- You know, because I thought,
- after I beat you...
- Yeah. I got it.
- Thanks for expediting.
- Yeah.
Do you need something?
Did you know that Harvey,
uh, was a prosecutor?
- No, he wasn't.
- Yeah. He was.
I've read every bio at the firm.
People work for the da's office,
it's on their bio.
Well, we ran into Cameron Dennis
this morning.
- The da?
- Yeah.
He says that Harvey's
the best Ada he's ever had.
No. Come here.
See? Nothing about
being a prosecutor.
Yeah.
I need you to go on a double date
with me and Jenny.
Yeah. Not going to happen.
You have to. Listen to me.
Louis warned her.
About you and me.
What...
How did he even get...
You know how.
Because he walked in
right after you kissed me.
If you say no, she's going to think
something is going on between us.
Okay. I'll go.
- Thank you.
- Freaking Louis.
Oh... is this Harvey?
Okay, you are definitely
sending me that photo.
Rachel: Westlaw lists him
as prosecutor of record
on pages and pages of cases.
I told you.
I don't get it. Why wouldn't he have
this on his bio?
Because, maybe he has
something to hide.
See the money,
wanna stay for your meal
get another piece of pie
for your wife
everybody wanna know how it feel
everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
me and missy is so early
busy, busy making money
all right!
All step back I'm 'bout to dance
the greenback boogie
"It touches some
idealistic core of your being
"where even the greatest cynic
has not given up hope.
"That's why we listen to music."
Oh, that's beautiful, Louis.
Really.
And I think
your decision to leave law
to become a music critic
is in everyone's best interest.
Okay. I was quoting
Peter sellars.
I just got $1,000 a head tickets
to Nixon in China.
Are you two dating now?
Should I come back?
Sit down, Harvey.
I love it when you talk to me like
my third grade teacher,
Mrs. Coe.
Gentlemen.
Malcolm price died last week.
Truly great loss for humanity.
You want to mock the dead? Fine.
But his tabloid, nothing but the truth,
has made us a fortune.
Price has left his estate,
10 companies
including the tabloid,
to his two daughters,
Madison and Kelsey.
We have been asked to divide the assets
up fairly.
And I'm here why?
Because they hate each other.
Malcolm structured the will to bring
them back together.
You have a knack for bringing parties
together who don't see eye to eye.
So why is he here?
Because Madison price
requested him.
You sure she's not
mixing him up with me?
Hardman had me do some contract work for
her a couple of years back.
- So I guess I made an impression.
- Right.
So you each get a sister.
You think pitting us against each other
is fair to Louis' client?
Please. Dividing
financial assets?
- You couldn't shine my shoes.
- Someone should.
Well, actually, I personally shine my
own shoes. So there you go.
Well, lucky them.
How come you always ask Donna,
"Donna, by the way,
"those are really nice shoes that Louis
has on."
Gentlemen.
We're on the same side.
And although I would not
choose to have you both on this,
that is how it fell. So...
I expect you to put your differences
aside and work together on this,
so that everyone can be happy.
Can you manage that this time?
She's always hated me.
Well, maybe this is a chance to put
all that behind you.
I'd like that. Really, I would.
But maddie... I don't think so.
Maybe she'll surprise you.
Kelsey's a bitch.
She doesn't deserve any of it.
Well, I'm afraid your father didn't
share that point of view.
According to his will,
we were meant...
To find a division of these companies
that makes both of you happy.
But I want to make sure that...
That you're happy.
You want to know what
will make me happy?
Whatever makes her miserable.
It's simple.
Kelsey: I want
nothing but the truth.
My father and I
worked together on it for years and...
Madison: It made me crazy.
The two of them
pretending that tabloid was literature.
Kelsey: It means
everything to me.
All I want is...
Madison: To sell off
that piece of garbage
and for her to get
as little as possible.
What made her so mad at you?
She blames me for our dad leaving her
mother and marrying mine.
How can she think
that's your fault?
Because her mother got pregnant, and
used it to rope in my dad.
And then, little Kelsey became the
center of his universe.
Do you know what's it's like to have
someone hate you out of pure jealousy?
We'll get you the paper.
Do you know what it's like?
To watch someone else
get all the attention,
when you know that you're
twice the person they are?
She's not getting that paper.
- Maddie.
- Kelsey.
- Louis.
- Harvey.
- Doctor.
- Chevy.
- Nice.
- Good meeting?
- Yeah, we connected. You?
We're on the same page.
Louis: Hmm.
What was, uh,
Kelsey looking for?
I don't know.
Why don't you ask Jenny?
You seem to like talking to her.
(Typing)
No, Mike,
that's not distracting.
- I was just waiting.
- For what?
To not be distracting.
How come Harvey doesn't talk about
working for the da's office?
- Who told you that?
- Cameron Dennis.
We ran into him this morning.
They're having dinner.
So, that's why he wouldn't tell me
where he was going.
What's going on, Donna?
Let it go.
Don't ask Harvey about this.
- What's the big secret?
- It's no secret, just...
Don1.
And what are we talking about?
The price sisters.
Those girls.
Do we really have to play nice with
Louis? I want to crush him.
You want to crush him?
Get over to the paper, kick the tires,
and figure out what it's worth.
I thought we were supposed to use the
independent valuations.
What? You think he's going
to play by the rules?
I know he won't.
That's why you better be
three steps ahead of him.
Because I can guarantee you, Louis will
be two steps ahead of you.
Donna: Speak of the devil.
Her majesty's here to see you.
- I heard that.
- You were meant to.
- Gentlemen.
- Your highness.
Okay. You know what?
That's exactly why I'm here.
To be mocked?
No. To set clear ground rules
to keep the negotiation aboveboard.
Absolutely. No kicking, no biting,
and no rabbit punches.
And now, you're mocking the ground
rules.
No, I'm just mocking you.
Point one.
We both agree to use
the independent valuations.
Absolutely. Good point.
Point two.
You do not
call Jessica in to mediate.
This is you and me.
You afraid mom's
going to take my side?
No, I know mom's
going to take your side.
- Because I'd be right.
- Point three.
Chinese wall.
You can't access
any internal documents that I create.
Let's make Jessica proud.
We do this right,
everyone walks away happy.
Wonderful.
Don't worry.
We'll still crush him.
- I heard that.
- You were meant to.
(Inhaling deeply)
Care to make a wager?
Our job is to make both sisters happy.
How do we know who wins?
Both: We'll know.
Usual amount?
No. I think we should change
it up this time.
I win, I get Mike.
You can't bet me
like I'm chattel, Louis.
Harvey: It's not like
he's going to win.
Louis: One month.
Ten days.
- Harvey.
- Two weeks.
- Nine days.
- Harvey!
All right. You know what?
Fine. Ten days.
And in return?
Well, that's tough. Because anything you
have, I wouldn't want.
What, uh...
You're going to bet me for nothing?
Harvey?
Harvey specter.
Alexandra Leeds.
I hear you're working for the attorney
general's office.
And you're fighting
for the oppressive capitalists.
Winning for the
oppressive capitalists.
Good for you.
We should have lunch.
Catch up.
Who told you I was
coming here tonight?
No one.
I haven't seen you in five years.
You want to catch up?
You want something from me.
And it isn't lunch.
I want to talk about
Cameron Dennis.
Six feet. Pisces. Wavy hair.
I'm serious.
I haven't worked for Cameron in over a
decade. What's there to talk about?
The Attorney General's
investigating allegations
that he systematically buried
evidence to get convictions.
So, talk to people
who actually work with the guy.
Yeah, that's the problem. He's still
their boss. Nobody is talking.
Neither am I. Over lunch or anywhere
else. So, best of luck.
Harvey.
I was hoping for some lunch.
I'm having you subpoenaed.
To testify before a grand jury.
Enjoy your dinner.
Give Cameron my best.
Hey. Harvey.
Glad you could make it. How are you?
Tell me about the bullshit run-in that
you staged this morning.
How long did you have to wait so that
you could pretend
to be surprised to see me?
Ten minutes.
You're never early, but I didn't want
to cut it too close.
Well, I also just had another little
run-in with Alexandra Leeds.
(Sighs)
You really want to
drag me into this?
Calm down, Harvey. I'm not dragging
you into anything.
They're dragging me into this.
It's election year nonsense,
and I wanted to warn you.
So you asked me here to warn me?
Yeah, and to reassure myself that
you've got my back.
How bad is it?
It's nothing I can't handle,
but I'm glad you're here.
Look, Harvey.
Whatever differences we had,
we were a good team.
The truth is that,
if anything taints
the work that we did,
it will be bad for both of us.
Is that a threat?
Not at all. It's just reality.
We put away bad people, Harvey.
We fought tough battles
and we won.
I taught you how to win.
That's not exactly what
you taught me, though.
I know that you didn't
always approve of the means,
but we both know that the end result
was always right.
You're still the best
smooth talker I know.
Use it now. Talk your way out
of this. Settle.
Because if this goes to court, there are
skeletons to be found.
They won't find them.
You want to bank on that?
I have your back.
I am not volunteering anything.
But if push comes to shove,
I won't perjure myself.
Not even for you.
(Soul music playing)
How was dinner
with the antichrist?
Subpoena came for you.
What are you going to do?
What would you do?
I'm sorry. Are you feeling okay?
You just asked my advice.
All these years?
Yeah, that's a first.
You were there.
What would you do?
I'd tell them everything.
I'd watch Cameron go down.
I'd throw a party,
I'd drink champagne,
I'd go to bed, and I'd sleep like a
baby after I did it.
Really? Don't equivocate.
He's poison, Harvey.
Leaving there was huge.
You could have gone
down a dark road.
And I am telling you,
I would not have followed.
Mike: I just got back
from the paper.
This place,
it's a growing asset.
There's opportunity
for expansion.
If we get this thing for Kelsey,
I think she's set.
I saw Elvis there.
Great.
That's exciting.
Am I interrupting something?
- Dinner didn't go well?
- It was okay.
Old times. (Music stops)
If that's how you
want to play it.
Let's talk about
this proposal for Louis.
(Clears throat)
You know what? Why don't you
take a run at it?
Get the best deal you can.
You bet me, and now, you're hanging
me out to dry?
That's fine. I'll do it.
And I'll win.
Oh, did you decide what you want him
to pay you when I win?
His tickets to Nixon in China.
You want to go to the opera?
No, but Louis does. And making him miss
it will be amusing.
So you get nothing.
You are betting me for nothing.
- Are you still talking?
- Right.
- So, did you find a date for tonight?
- Yep.
And?
And we'll see you there.
What?
I thought that's what
you said you wanted.
To sit with you and Jenny and have her
seeing into my brain the whole time?
Seeing what?
You do remember
that we kissed, right?
I remember.
It will be okay.
(Knocking)
Hi. Uh, is this a good time to talk
about division of assets?
Is there a better time, or...
Yes. When Harvey's available.
Harvey asked me to handle it.
- He thinks you can beat me?
- Prove him wrong.
What's there to lose?
Except for Nixon in China,
of course.
What do you have for me?
Okay. So, there
are 10 companies.
We propose that Kelsey takes companies
one, three, seven, and nine.
So that gives us...
52.3% of the assets.
Hmm. Generous. But, no.
Alternatively, we propose that Kelsey
takes companies
one, two, four, and eight.
That gives you...
54.6%. No.
Do you have a
counterproposal, or...
Okay. Uh, Kelsey takes companies
one, seven, eight, and nine.
- No.
- Louis, that gives you
60% of the assets.
Yes. But, no.
What is it your client wants?
Well, your offer makes it infinitely
clear what your client wants.
The tabloid.
And what my client wants is for your
client to not get what she wants.
So, you can't have
the tabloid. Period.
You are legally required
to take these offers to your client.
So, bring me up
on ethics charges.
Or report me to your supervisor.
Oh, wait. Shit.
I am your supervisor.
Hold on one second.
Go ahead.
What are your complaints?
Have any? No? Really?
We're supposed to find a fair and
equitable settlement, Louis.
Well, then, you go
run and tell Jessica.
Oh, wait. That would
be breaking the rules.
And then you'd have
to come work for me.
So why don't you run along now
and get Harvey
and tell him to get off his ass and join
the negotiations.
Because you just failed.
When you left the da's office,
you said you were done.
You had learned enough.
And that you were ready to move on.
Was that just bullshit?
You were the one
who wanted me to have trial experience.
You said that Cameron was the only one
that I should learn from.
And what exactly
did he teach you?
Harvey, why did you leave?
He had a case.
I caught him burying a key piece of
evidence he was obligated to turn over.
The guy was guilty. The defense would
have used it to let him walk.
All right. What kind
of exposure do you have?
I told him no. He didn't listen.
Then, you were obligated
to report him.
Which is why I left.
Why didn't you tell me this
at the time?
Because you put me there,
Jessica. To be mentored.
Okay. And it occurred to me, that might
have been exactly
what you wanted me to learn.
For the record, it wasn't.
I'm going to represent you
at this deposition.
I'm going to try to
keep you from talking.
But I think you should.
- He was my mentor.
- He is a public servant.
- The standards are higher.
He was my mentor.
And I am not going to be the one
to expose him
any more than
I'd ever turn on you.
(Pop music playing)
Jenny: Worst dating story...
Identical twins.
I was a lab rat for their
social experiment.
They were trying to prove
that women were shallow
and can't see
beyond the surface.
And they wanted to get laid.
Yes. That, too.
Good times.
So you slept with them both.
Jenny: Almost.
Turns out they weren't
identical after all.
Wow. Excuse me. I am just going to run
to the ladies' room.
- Oh, I'll go with you.
- Okay.
What's wrong, Mikey?
Tough day at the office?
Didn't see you.
It could have been worse.
That's good.
So, you and Rachel. How long have you
guys been dating?
You know how lawyers and clients grow
close over the course of a trial.
When we kicked your
ass in the mock trial,
we, uh...
Bonded.
You know, in the real world, dating
clients
is a violation of ethics. Right?
Good thing it's not
the real world.
Because I intend to violate those
ethics all night.
You know the funny thing?
I always thought
you'd get there first.
- I'll tell you how she is.
- Shut up, Kyle.
Someone might think
you're jealous.
you're a dick.
Oh, wait. Somebody already does.
That's good.
You should write that one down.
- Do you keep a journal of these things?
- Just finish your tofu.
- So, how did you two meet?
- Um...
I dated his best friend.
I know. It's awful. But he was a bad guy
and I didn't see it.
Mike showed me.
The truth is, I...
I think there was always
something there with us.
But nothing happened until Trevor and I
were totally done.
Never?
Well, we did kiss once.
Jenny: Hey. Having fun?
Loads. Right, Mike?
I think we're going to go.
- What? No. We're having fun. Come on.
- Yeah. I'm just tired.
- Yeah.
- Kyle, really. Just...
Okay. Kyle, just, you know...
Kyle: What? What's your problem?
Stop it. She doesn't like it.
Oh, my god. That guy is
such a tool.
So what? He's not your date.
Yeah? Well, I have
to work with him.
That's not why it bothers you.
It's because he's with Rachel
and you know it.
Oh, my god. Jenny,
we've been over this.
I've seen the way
you look at her.
I've seen it before.
It's the way you used to look at me
when I was with Trevor.
- Jenny, I...
- I'm going home, Mike.
Decide what you want.
In or out.
I like you.
A lot.
But you can't have both.
I worked as an
assistant district attorney
for the county of New York
for two years.
Leeds: Tell me about your relationship
with Cameron Dennis.
Vague.
Did you and district attorney
Cameron Dennis work closely together?
He was my boss.
He supervised all my cases.
And were you personally close?
- Subjective.
- Ajudge would allow it.
And yet, there's not one here.
Do you really think,
by deposing him on the stand,
you're going to intimidate him?
I think deposing him here
will let him know what it will be like
if this evidence
is brought fonlvard at trial.
You're not getting to trial.
If your client doesn't perjure himself
right now, I won't have to.
Were you and Cameron
Dennis close? Personally?
He was my mentor. That's a hard
relationship to define.
Moving on, counselor.
All right. We don't have to talk
about Mr. Dennis.
Let's talk about you,
Mr. Specter.
In two years,
you handled 18,362 cases.
Thirty-six cases a day.
That's beyond impressive.
Thank you.
You took 147 to trial,
winning them all.
Don't go to trial if you're not
going to win.
Why did you leave?
An attorney by the name of Jessica
Pearson
helped me get through law school.
And she felt that I could use
trial experience.
But I always planned
on ending up at her firm
and paying her back by earning that firm
outrageous settlements.
- How am I doing?
- Could do better.
You two think
that this is a joke.
Argumentative.
You're damn right
it's argumentative.
Because he knows that
laws have been broken,
- and he has an obligation to report it.
- Miss Leeds...
But if this is the way
you want to play it,
the Attorney General has given me a
broad mandate to uncover what went on.
And it need not be limited
to Mr. Dennis.
Were you part of
the problem, Mr. Specter?
Jessica: Vague.
I'll rephrase.
In your capacity as assistant district
attorney in the county of New York,
did you knowingly suppress evidence in
violation of the aba rules of conduct,
the ndaa standards,
and the New York state
bar rule 8.4, section c?
My client would like to exercise his
fifth amendment rights at this time.
I hear you botched the settlement by
negotiating against yourself.
I didn't...
You let Louis know the one thing that
was most important to our client.
Yes, I made a mistake.
But Louis made one, too.
Well, he didn't mention that.
Yes, he knows what our client
wants.
But now, we know the
one thing his client wants.
She doesn't care
about winning, Harvey.
She just wants
our client to lose.
Okay. Well, that's good.
So what's next?
We lose.
We give her the tabloid.
Well, how does that
make our client happy?
We let Madison have the paper.
And then, we take everyone who works
there and we start a new one.
They all love Kelsey.
Nothing but the truth is just a name.
We let Madison have it.
I have taught you
a thing or two.
Well, I see that
you're up to speed. Well, as am I.
Um... I noticed there were
some employee issues at the tabloid.
You know, contracts
about to expire.
So, I just want
to let you guys know
that I, uh, went ahead and locked up
all the key employees.
Just to protect us.
Since we're all
working on this together. Right?
- Mmmhmm.
- Good.
- He knows.
- He can't.
- He does.
- I was careful.
I deleted
every file from the server.
The only time any paper trail
left my locked desk is when
I faxed it to Kelsey.
Oh, you faxed it.
From the large machine
that stores all the information you put
in it to be printed back later
- by anyone who has your code?
- He can't do that.
We have a Chinese wall thingy.
Oh, god. He's going
to beat us, isn't he?
Look. He knows what we're up to,
but he couldn't
keep his tactics to himself.
So, we can use that against him.
And that's how
we'll crush Louis.
Refresher course, Harvey. You and Louis
aren't opponents on this one.
You're working together.
Like captain & tennille?
Well, if so, he's tennille.
Mike: Who?
You need to come with me.
- What, am I in trouble?
- Yeah, Harvey. You are.
You going to buy me a drink before
you screw me?
Sit down, Harvey. Listen to what
she has to say.
You've got me
trembling in my boots.
You're a small fish, and you don't even
swim in the pond anymore.
But if I have to eat you alive to get to
Cameron Dennis, I will.
This is my case against him.
Falsifying DNA tests.
Coerced confessions.
Testimony buried.
If you have all this,
why do you need me?
Because this is circumstantial.
You have the crimes, but you can't
physically tie them to Cameron.
He's a dirty public servant.
And I think it's why you left.
Your record was too good
to just walk away.
- Maybe I got greedy.
- Harvey.
- I'm not testifying.
- You're being stubborn.
And this isn't one where
you get to make the call.
I'm sorry.
I've done all I can.
It wasn't just his cases
he cheated on.
Hector avila. Take a look.
You think you were
really that great?
You think your great track record was
because of your skill?
I've got two theories
here, Harvey.
Either you're wasting your time
protecting a man who screwed you
from the beginning,
or you didn't just
know he did this.
You participated. In which case,
I'll have you disbarred.
Come on. Come on. Damn it.
(Grunting)
What are you doing?
Uh, nothing. I'm just sending some
faxes. (Clears throat)
Stand down.
(Sighs)
They're stuck, Donna.
What are you going to do?
(Whispering)
I'm the fax whisperer.
Okay. That's ridiculous, right?
I've tried everything. I hit... I've
already done that, and it didn't...
Whatever.
United international
wants to buy the tabloid?
Ah. Whatever you do,
don't say anything to Louis.
Kelsey price does
not want to sell.
- Not a word.
- Thanks.
Whoa.
Something explode in here?
Just doing some research.
Yeah. Because you always
do your own research.
Okay. Closed-door meeting with Donna,
with Jessica...
Dinner with some da you've
never even mentioned before. Is this...
All something
Cameron Dennis taught you?
Keep secrets from everyone because
you're so good,
you don't need anyone's help?
There's an investigation
into evidence tampering.
I've been asked to testify
against my old boss.
Or face charges myself.
You could be disbarred?
If I'm found guilty.
Are you guilty?
Not of evidence tampering.
I would never do that.
Of anything else?
Anything I ever did, you put me in front
of an unbiased judge,
I walk away clean.
You put me in a courtroom
with a grand jury?
Anything can happen.
So, are you going to testify?
I'm not sure what choice I have.
Well, some dickhead
once told me that,
when they put a gun to your head, it's
not just give in or be killed.
There are 146 other options.
You'll figure something out.
(Knocking)
I'll have a proposal
for you in the morning.
And I think we'll all be happy.
All right?
Night.
He took the bait?
Like shooting fish in a barrel.
Good work.
Where you going?
I just might take your advice.
Cameron: Well, the tides are turning.
Are you turning with them, Harvey?
Did they turn you?
Hector avila.
You don't even know, do you?
This is some old case?
It's my old case.
And you buried evidence.
You wearing a wire, Harvey?
No, you're not.
I can tell.
I'm not that easy
to read anymore, Cameron.
You are to me.
Hector avila.
Was he guilty, whoever he was?
- It was my case.
- Guilty is guilty.
That's not the way
the system works.
The system is broken
and you know it.
It's not reasonable doubt.
Juries want to be sure
without a shadow of a doubt.
- It was my case.
- You worked for me.
They were all my cases.
You're a disappointment.
No. You're the disappointment.
You could have been da yourself.
You are twice the lawyer than any of the
pricks lined up to run against me.
But you sold out.
You help rich people keep their money.
That's all you do.
I stack my value to society against
yours and I win by a mile.
So you're selling me out?
We both know they don't want to put you
in jail. That's not what this is about.
Walk away, Cameron. Make a deal.
Let someone else be da, and all of this?
It goes away.
Otherwise? You know
what happens if you talk.
They start reopening cases.
Maybe Hector avila walks away.
He murdered once.
He'll murder again.
You do remember him, don't you?
Oh, I remember them all.
Maxwell rankin? What was it, uh,
34 or 35 women that he raped?
Alberto plank? You remember him?
He burned his children alive?
You'll open the floodgates, Harvey.
You want that on your conscience?
Then, make a deal. It's on you to
keep them in jail.
Okay.
Okay, Harvey.
You win.
This isn't winning.
Good to see you, Harvey.
Let's do it again soon.
So your client is really willing to give
Madison nothing but the truth?
You made it clear
it was non-negotiable.
I convinced my client
to settle, and...
She wants to move on.
You sure there isn't anything that you
want to, uh, disclose?
Nope. I think we're good.
Then, we're good.
Everybody's happy.
Mike: Mmm-hmm.
As clams.
Thank you, Louis.
You, um... happy with the deal?
Yeah. As a matter
of fact, I am. You?
(Chuckles)
You don't even know
the half of it.
Don't I?
Are you happy that your client
got the paper or that you
turned around and sold it?
You didn't think
I knew about that, did you?
You want to know
why I'm happy, Louis?
I'm happy because when you read over
that offer from united international,
I wanted you to read that.
I wanted you to sell to them.
Because the thing you didn't know
is that yesterday,
Kelsey price bought
united international.
You shouldn't go behind
people's backs, Louis.
You shouldn't try and access information
that's none of your business.
- It could backfire.
- Mmm.
I think we need
to talk to Harvey.
- I'm sorry, Harvey.
- You set me up.
No, Louis. You set yourself up.
The sales offer was meaningless
until you read it.
This is cheating.
You cheated, Louis.
You broke the rules,
and you have to pay the price.
People may think that lawyers will do
anything. That they can do anything.
Now, I'm not willing
to accept that. Okay?
You can't go skirting
the rules and justify it
because you think
someone else broke the rules.
Okay? You cheated, and you lost.
End of story.
Harvey, I won.
His playacting by the fax machine?
That was so obvious.
I found out Kelsey owned
united international.
I thought, "if they wanted the paper so
badly,
how much would they overpay for it?"
50%.
Harvey, you overpaid 50% for a business
so buried in expenses
from the employee deals that I made that
it can barely stay afloat.
And then, all I had to do was convince
Madison to sit back,
have fun, watch her sister
fail miserably. Iwon.
Your client got what she wanted.
So did ours.
Jessica asked
to make everyone happy.
Everyone's happy. It's a draw.
Just hold on a second.
You tell me the truth right now.
- Is this a win to you?
- Fine, Louis. You win.
You were a step ahead.
You got Mike. Ten days.
You think I want him now?
I just wiped the floor with him.
How can I help you?
I'm not going to let him take the fall
for that asshole.
Have a seat.
Harvey didn't see it
for a long time.
I mean, Cameron's good
when he wants to be.
You know how ijudge
a man's character?
Not by how he treats his equals, but by
how he treats the underlings.
The lowest rungs on the ladder.
You always impressed me
in that regard.
Thank you.
Harvey would never use that, and
he'd kill me if he knew I had it.
But, can you help him?
Can you use this to help him?
Is Harvey punishing
you for something?
- Louis.
- No. You lost?
You have to work for him?
I lost. And then, he said he didn't want
me. He farmed me out.
Oh, I'm so sorry. Is there anything
I can do to help?
What?
That
what are you talking about?
(Sighs)
I wanted you for months,
Rachel. I flirted. I... I... I made up
some scheme where we were married.
And you made it clear.
You don't date
anyone from the office.
Until I start seeing
someone else...
Okay. You're delusional.
Why did you bring
Kyle on that date?
Because it was last-minute
and because you needed me to
help convince your girlfriend
that you don't like me.
You did it to get to me.
This is crazy. It's just stupid.
You don't even
like the guy, Rachel.
Jenny comes to drop off a suit at the
office, and what do you do?
You kissed me.
You know, I seem to recall you
kissing me, too.
Yeah. That's the problem.
I did and it was great.
But it's too late.
You were too late.
- And I can't do any of this.
- Do what?
This. This... this... you joking about
your first time.
Or... or rubbing my shoulders or...
Or touching my arm.
You're playing
with me and you know it.
What I know is,
you're playing with me, too.
You kept flirting with me long after
you started dating her.
Yeah, well,
that's going to stop.
Good.
You know,
and while you're at it,
no more running to me for favors or
asking me for help.
How about you find yourself
some other paralegal?
Because as far
as I'm concerned, we're done.
Cameron: Yeah,
I forget what excuse he used this time.
I've heard them all before.
Uh, can you give us a minute?
Wow. Jessica.
I've spoken to Alexandra Leeds.
She told me about
the deal you cut.
What do you want me to say?
(Chuckling)
Hmm.
This is a copy.
I'm driving over to
the Attorney General's office right now.
If she doesn't tell me you've cut a new
deal by the time I get there,
she gets the original.
And then, I give her the proof.
You don't have the proof.
Don't I?
Cut a new deal.
And if you ever mess
with one of mine again,
Alexandra gets that anyway.
You don't have to testify.
They don't need you anymore.
Cameron made a deal?
He made a deal.
To sell you out.
But I made my own deal.
He'll be stepping down. Spending some
quality time with his family.
How exactly did you manage that?
Not your concern. But you're in
the clear, Harvey.
Some people would be
happy with that news.
That son of a bitch.
Clifford danner. He was 18.
I put him in jail 12 years ago.
Kid's been rotting in prison
his whole adult life.
And?
He's innocent.
Cameron buried the evidence.
If I'd had it...
Do you have enough to overturn?
I don't know.
Jessica:
So, what are you going to do?
I'm going to get him out.